brandingmagazine.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Brandingmag

The following policy provides you with details of how we collect and process your personal data through your use of the sites owned by Brandium, Inc, including Brandingmag.com, Branding.news, RebelsRulers.com, BrandingOverTea.com, and BrandingNite.com. Our [“Branding Mag” iPad app](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/branding-mag/id879914284?ls=1&mt=8) is an official Brandium, Inc. Ltd. product, so all of our policies apply there, as well. In the following, “we” shall refer to these online properties.

By providing us with your data, you warrant that you are over 13 years of age.

**Do we collect personal data?**  
Depending upon your use of Our Sites, we may collect some or all of the following personal data: name, gender, business/company name and details, job title, contact information (e.g., email addresses and telephone numbers), demographic information (e.g.,location, preferences and interests), financial information (e.g., credit / debit card numbers), IP address, web browser type and version, and operating system.

If you register on Our Sites using your account on Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin, or Google, or accounts from other third-party services, then the only data we’ll receive from those accounts are the ones necessary for registration (e.g., name, surname, email address, company name, and job title).

We do not collect any Sensitive Data about you. Sensitive Data refers to data that includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health, and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

**How do we collect personal data?**  
We may collect data about you when you provide the data directly to us (e.g., by filling in forms on Our Sites or by sending us direct emails). We may also collect certain data from you via cookies and similar technologies while you use Our Sites, once you’ve agreed to them or failed to disagree.

We may receive data from third parties such as analytics providers (e.g., Google) based outside the EU; advertising networks (e.g., Facebook) based outside the EU; search information providers (e.g., Google) based outside the EU; and providers of technical, payment, and delivery services (e.g., data brokers or aggregators).

**What about children’s data?**  
Our Sites are not intended for or targeted at children under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13 years of age. If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 13 years of age, then please contact us at info@brandingmag.com with the subject [CHILD DATA] so that we may delete the information.

**Why do we need your personal data?**  
We only ask for and use the necessary data to ensure the following points:  
Offering a customised web experience, with ads that are relevant to you;  
Improving Our Sites based on how you and our other visitors interact with them, to offer you a seamless and ever-improved experience;  
Offering you access to our free content (see Free Downloads) and paid content (if you download our paid products or become a paid subscriber);  
Sending you our weekly newsletter (if you have subscribed to it) containing premium insights from international industry thought leaders, recommended events, and other relevant news;  
Send information or content to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means and send you marketing communications relating to our business;  
Promote use of our services to you and share promotional and information content with you in accordance with your communication preferences.

**For how long do we store your personal data?**  
We keep your personal data as long as we have your consent. If you wish to receive a copy of the personal data that you have agreed to share with us, then please email us at info@brandingmag.com with the subject [My Personal Data].  
If you wish to remove your consent and have your data deleted (meaning you will not receive any future branding insights from our thought leaders and might stop benefitting from your subscription if you request that your account be deleted), then please email us at info@brandingmag.com with the subject [Consent Removal].

**How do we protect your personal data?**  
Any personal data received will only be used to fill your order (Store Billing / PayPal / Mobilpay) or to communicate with you if you subscribed to our newsletter. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit/debit card processing on our behalf. We do not store credit card details nor do we share financial details with any third parties.

We have put in place the appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being altered, disclosed, or accidentally lost, used, or accessed in an unauthorised way. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors, and other third parties who have a business need to know such data. These third parties include:

  * Service providers who provide IT and system administration services.
  * Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers
  * Government bodies that require us to report processing activities.
  * Third parties such as copywriters, customer support and virtual assistants.
  * Third parties to whom we sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets.

We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

**What is our Cookie Policy?**  
Cookies are used by nearly all websites and do not harm your system.

We use cookies (small text files sent by your computer each time you visit Our Sites, unique to your account or your browser) to understand your browsing preferences and show you relevant ads, but not for collecting personal data. This also helps us to develop and improve Our Sites, as well as our products and/or services, in response to what you might need or want.

If you allow cookies to be used, your personal information may be stored by third parties such as Google AdSense, Google Analytics, Hotjar, HubSpot, and Mailchimp.

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of Our Sites may become inaccessible or not function properly.

When accessing Our Sites, you will be able to express your consent regarding our use of cookies. If you want to change your settings, then you can clear your cache and re-enter Our Sites – the pop-up regarding cookies will reappear and you can choose your preference. If you wish to check or change which types of cookies you accept, then this can usually be altered within your browser settings. You can block cookies at any time by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the delivery of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of Our Sites.

In regards to Session Cookies: these are only stored on your computer during your web session and are automatically deleted when you close your browser – they usually store an anonymous session ID allowing you to browse a website without having to log in to each page, but they do not collect any personal data from your computer.

In regards to Persistent Cookies: these are stored as files on your computer and they remain there when you close your web browser. Persistent Cookies can be read by the websites that created them when you visit those websites again. We use persistent cookies for Google Analytics. The third party analytics companies we work with may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online products and services. Their collection and use of information is subject to their own privacy policies.

Please note that all third parties who advertise on Our Sites (e.g., advertising networks and providers of external services such as web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytics/performance cookies or retargeting cookies. The latter may also be referred to as Pixels, meaning tiny pieces of JavaScript code that we have incorporated into each of our web pages to provide a series of functions for transmitting application-specific events and user-defined data to Facebook or Google. These Pixels record information about your browsing session, which it sends to Facebook or Google, along with a hashed version of the Facebook ID and/or URL viewed. This helps us serve you better with personalized content based on your preferences and interactions.

**How do you deal with third-party links?**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on Our Sites. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies; therefore, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of Our Sites and welcome any feedback about the third-party sites we associate with.

_This policy was updated on 05/25/2018. We reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will notify you over email if you are subscribed to our list and update the date of our notice here on this page._

_For more information, please contact us via info@brandingmag.com._
